We3social is a multi-chain social decentralized application software based on moonbeam
which can provide users with peer-to-peer social and information sharing functions
Let's take a look at how to use We3social's DAPP
First
open Tokenpocket or Imtoken
or other wallets that support the moonbeam public chain
Then enter the We3social address in the browser
check and agree to the terms of service
and click "Start Exploring".
If you are logging in for the first time
you first need to click "Register",
then use any other email address to complete the account registration
and you can log in after successful registration
After entering the interface
you can choose to click the "Personal Center" icon in the upper left corner to complete the soul binding function in the settings
so that the system can provide you with a recommendation function to facilitate other users to find you
After completing the binding
return to the home page
and you can see that the system has automatically pushed some users for you
You can click on a user to view his profile and needs
and send a request to add WeChat
If you want to select the users to push by yourself
you can click here to customize the filter criteria you need
Anyone can see the DID identities of other users on the DID push square and get in touch with them
If you cannot filter the partners you need
you can click the "+ sign" in the lower right corner of the "Demand Square",
first edit your demand content
then add tags
and finally click "Publish".
After the release is successful
other users can take the initiative to contact you through the content you publish
All the posts you have published and the friends you have made can be viewed through the "Personal Center" page
Finally
We3social also provides a DID identity purchase function
which is the value-added service part of the project
Users can choose to pay to register for Moonbeam DID to obtain additional services
First click the "DID Unlock" option on the "Personal Center" page
then click the "Price" at the bottom
connect to the Moonbeam wallet and send the signature to complete the payment
Currently the project is in the early testing stage
so we don't need to pay
just send the signature